Guide to the GW Hatchet records, 1904-2007 RG0114
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Images, 1970 ca. - 1980 ca.; RG0114 Series 2; 1.5 Linear feet (Box 2, Box 3, Box 1)
  - Negatives, undated (Box 2, Folder 27.12)
  - Three basketball players with coach, 1968 ca. (Box 3, Folder 28.1)
  - GW basketball game vs. Virginia, 1970 ca. (Box 3, Folder 28.2)
  - Coach with GW basketball player #34, 1970 ca. (Box 3, Folder 28.3)
  - Howard Sacher, undated (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Negatives of Program board personalities, undated (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - University Yard, undated (Box 3, Folder 31.1)
  - Lisner Hall, undated (Box 3, Folder 31.2)
  - Four men working, undated (Box 3, Folder 31.3)
  - Experiment theater, undated (Box 3, Folder 32.1)
  - Experiment theater, undated (Box 3, Folder 32.2)
  - America two night, undated (Box 3, Folder 32.3)
  - Ramona, undated (Box 3, Folder 32.4)
  - Lima, undated (Box 3, Folder 32.5)
  - Camp David, undated (Box 3, Folder 33.1)
  - Reporting, undated (Box 3, Folder 33.2)
  - Camp David, undated (Box 3, Folder 33.3)
  - Joe Salcetti, undated (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Nan Smith, undated (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Jayne Spain, undated (Box 3, Folder 36.1)
  - Dean Spain, undated (Box 3, Folder 36.2)
  - B. Swain, undated (Box 3, Folder 37.1)
  - Negative of a man, undated (Box 3, Folder 37.2)
- Newspapers, 1971-1991; RG0114 Series 3; 19.5 Linear feet
  This series contains newspapers. These GW Hatchet copies cover the dates 1971-1991.
  Formerly ACC#563
  This series has a container list in electronic form, please ask staff for assistance.
- Newspapers and posters, 1992-1997; RG0114 Series 4; 0.25 Linear feet (Box 1)
  This series contains one bound volume of newspapers and campus posters. This material covers 1992-97. The bound volume covers the year 1996-97.
  Formerly ACC#643
  - The Fine Art of Campus Life, 1992-1993 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    General note
    2 posters
  - The Fine Art of Campus Life, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - The Fine Art of Campus Life [different version], 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - The Fine Art of Campus Life, 1994-1995 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Colonial Convocation, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Marvin's Rockin School House, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Black History Celebration, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Black History Celebration, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Marvin Gras, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Family Weekend - Open House, 10/15/1993-10/17/1993 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    2 copies
  - The George Washington Connection [map of campus and buildings], c.1995, 1995 ca. (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - A Convocation in honor of the life of Spirit of Dr. Martin Luther King, Jr., 1992 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Unity Week, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Seven Seconds in 1993 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Marc C. Abrahms, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - The World Mosaic, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Colonial Soccer, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - GW Inauguration Ball Committee, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Images and awards, 1939-1941; RG0114 Series 5; 0.25 Linear feet (Box SHARED Box 6)
  This series contains photographs, and awards. These images include subjects such as Abraham H. Simon, former editor of the Hatchet and the football team entering the "Tin Tabernacle" (old gym) in 1939. The awards were presented to the Hatchet by the Intercollegiate Newspaper Association (april 1941). These materials cover the dates 1939-1941.
  Formerly ACC#648
  - Photos and awards, 1939-1941 (Box SHARED Box 6, Folder 1)
    Photos of Abraham H. Simon, former editor of the Hatchet and the football team entering the "Tin Tabernacle" (old gym) in 1939. The awards were presented to the Hatchet by the Intercollegiate Newspaper Association (April 1941).
- Hatchet, unbound and bound volumes, 1904-2011; RG0114 Series 6; 32 Linear feet
  This series contains unbound and bound Hatchets, the student newspaper of GW. These newspapers range in date from 1904 to the present.
  Formerly ACC#280; call number LH1.H3
  - Hatchet Volume 1 (Copy 1), 1904-1905 (Volume 1 COPY 1)
    3 bound volumes
  - Hatchet Volume 1 (Copy 2), 1904-1905 (RG0114 Series 6, Box 1)
  - Hatchet Volume 1 (Copy 3), 1904-1905
  - Hatchet Volume 2 (Copy 1), 1905-1906 (Volume 2 COPY 1)
    2 bound volumes
  - Hatchet Volume 2 (Copy 2), 1905-1906 (RG0114 Series 6, Box 2)
  - Hatchet Volume 3 (Copy 1), 1906-1907 (Volume 3 COPY 1)
  - Hatchet Volume 3 (Copy 2), 1906-1907 (RG0114 Series 6, Box 2)
  - Hatchet Volume 4 (Copy 1), 1907-1908 (Volume 4)
    1 bound volume
  - Hatchet Volume 6 (Copy 1), 1909-1910 (Volume 6)
  - GW News Volume 1, 1910-1911 (Volume 1)
    Name change-Vol. 1 of The George Washington News
  - Hatchet Volume 8 (Copy 1), 1912-1913 (Volume 8)
  - Hatchet Volume 9 (Copy 1), 1913-1914 (Volume 9 COPY 1)
  - Hatchet Volume 9 (Copy 2), 1913-1914 (RG0114 Series 6, Box 2)
  - Hatchet Volume 11 (Copy 1), 1914-1915 (Volume 11)
    1 bound volume; No Vol. 10 printed; editors corrected for error of 1910-1911
  - Hatchet Volume 12 (Copy 1), 1915-1916 (RG0114 Series 6, Box 2)
  - Hatchet Volume 13 (Copy 1), 1916-1917
    On microfilm (missing No. 6)
  - Hatchet Volume 14 (Copy 1), 1917-1918 (RG0114 Series 6, Box 2)
    1 bound volume; (Missing No. 1)
  - Hatchet Volume 15 (Copy 1), 1918-1919 (RG0114 Series 6, Box 2)
  - Hatchet Volume 16 (Copy 1), 1919-1920 (Volume 16)
  - Hatchet Volume 17 (Copy 1), 1920-1921 (Volume 17)
  - Hatchet Volume 18 (Copy 1), 1921-1922 (Volume 18)
  - Hatchet Volume 19 (Copy 1), 1922-1923 (Volume 19)
  - Hatchet Volume 20 (Copy 1), 1923-1924 (Volume 20)
  - Hatchet Volume 21 (Copy 1), 1924-1925 (Volume 21 COPY 1)
    2 bound volumes; 31 issues, 12.5" x 19", 4 pages (avg.)
  - Hatchet Volume 21 (Copy 2), 1924-1925 (RG0114 Series 6, Box 3)
  - Hatchet Volume 22 (Copy 1), 1925-1926 (RG0114 Series 6, Box 4)
    2 bound volumes; 33 issues, 15" x 20.5", 4 pages (avg.)
  - Hatchet Volume 22 (Copy 2), 1925-1926 (RG0114 Series 6, Box 3)
  - Hatchet Volume 23 (Copy 1), 1926-1927 (RG0114 Series 6, Box 3)
    2 bound volumes; 32 issues, 15" x 20.5", 4 pages (avg. 1st semester), 6 pages (avg. 2nd semester)
  - Hatchet Volume 23 (Copy 2), 1926-1927 (RG0114 Series 6, Box 4)
  - Hatchet Volume 24 (Copy 1), 1927-1928 (RG0114 Series 6, Box 3)
    2 bound volumes; 31 issues, 15" x 20.5", 6 pages (avg.)
  - Hatchet Volume 24 (Copy 2), 1927-1928 (RG0114 Series 6, Box 4)
  - Hatchet Volume 25 (Copy 1), 1928-1929 (Volume 25 COPY 1)
    2 bound volumes; 31 issues plus one special issue, 15" x 20.75", 6 pages (avg. 1st semester), 4 pages (avg. 2nd semester)
  - Hatchet Volume 25 (Copy 2), 1928-1929 (RG0114 Series 6, Box 5)
    General
    Hatchet Volume 25 (Copy 2) inludes a copy of the Hatchet's Silver Anniversary Issue (dated May 15, 1929).
  - Hatchet, May 15, 1929 Silver Anniversary Issue
  - Hatchet Volume 26 (Copy 1), 1929-1930 (Volume 26 COPY 1)
    2 bound volumes; 32 issues plus one special issue, 14.75" x 21.75", 4-6 pages (avg. 1st semester), 4 pages (avg. 2nd semester)
  - Hatchet Volume 26 (Copy 2), 1929-1930 (RG0114 Series 6, Box 5)
  - Hatchet Volume 27 (Copy 1), 1930-1931 (Volume 27 COPY 1)
    2 bound volumes; 33 issues, 14.75" x 20.75", 6 pages (avg.)
  - Hatchet Volume 27 (Copy 2), 1930-1931 (RG0114 Series 6, Box 5)
  - Hatchet Volume 28 (Copy 1), 1931-1932 (RG0114 Series 6, Box 6)
    2 bound volumes; 36 issues, plus 6 Literary Supplements, 15" x 21.5" (Supplements: 10.5" x 15"), 6 pages (avg.), Supplements: 8 pages
  - Hatchet Volume 28 (Copy 2), 1931-1930 (RG0114 Series 6, Box 6)
  - Hatchet Volume 29 (Copy 1), 1932-1933 (RG0114 Series 6, Box 7)
    2 bound volumes; 35 issues, plus 7 Literary Supplements, 15" x 22.75" (Supplements: 10.5" x 14.25"), 6 pages (avg.), Supplements: 8 pages
  - Hatchet Volume 29 (Copy 2), 1932-1933 (RG0114 Series 6, Box 7)
  - Hatchet Volume 30 (Copy 1), 1933-1934 (RG0114 Series 6, Box 8)
    2 bound volumes; 35 issues, 15" x 22.75", 6 pages (avg.)
  - Hatchet Volume 30 (Copy 2), 1933-1934 (RG0114 Series 6, Box 8)
  - Hatchet Volume 31 (Copy 1), 1934-1935 (Volume 31 COPY 1)
  - Hatchet Volume 31 (Copy 2), 1934-1935 (RG0114 Series 6, Box 9)
  - Hatchet Volume 32 (Copy 1), 1935-1936 (RG0114 Series 6, Box 10)
    2 bound volumes; 34 issues, 15" x 22.75", 6 pages (avg.)
  - Hatchet Volume 32 (Copy 2), 1935-1936 (RG0114 Series 6, Box 10)
  - Hatchet Volume 33 (Copy 1), 1936-1937 (RG0114 Series 6, Box 11)
    3 bound volumes; 35 issues, 15" x 22", 6 pages (avg.)
  - Hatchet Volume 33 (Copy 2), 1936-1937 (RG0114 Series 6, Box 11)
  - Hatchet Volume 33 (Copy 3), 1936-1937 (RG0114 Series 6, Box 12)
  - Hatchet Volume 34 (Copy 1), 1937-1938 (RG0114 Series 6, Box 12)
    3 bound volumes; 33 issues, 15.5" x 22.25", 6 pages (avg.)
  - Hatchet Volume 34 (Copy 2), 1937-1938 (RG0114 Series 6, Box 13)
  - Hatchet Volume 34 (Copy 3), 1937-1938 (RG0114 Series 6, Box 13)
  - Hatchet Volume 35 (Copy 1), 1938-1939 (RG0114 Series 6, Box 14)
    3 bound volumes; 32 issues, 15.5" x 22.5", 6 pages (avg.)
  - Hatchet Volume 35 (Copy 2), 1938-1939 (RG0114 Series 6, Box 14)
  - Hatchet Volume 36 (Copy 1), 1939-1940 (Volume 36 COPY 1)
    2 bound volumes; 33 issues, 15.5" x 22.5", 6 pages (avg.)
  - Hatchet Volume 36 (Copy 2), 1939-1940 (RG0114 Series 6, Box 15)
  - Hatchet Volume 37 (Copy 1), 1940-1941 (RG0114 Series 6, Box 15)
    1 bound volume; First Tomahawk (April Fool's Issue) printed 33 issues plus Homecoming Supplement, 15.5" x 22.5" (Supplement:10.75" x 15.5"), 4-6 pages (avg.)
  - Hatchet Volume 38 (Copy 2), 1941-1942 (RG0114 Series 6, Box 16)
    1 bound volume; 31 issues, plus Alumni Supplement, 15.5" x 21.75" (Supplement: 10.5"x 15.5"), 4 pages (avg.)
  - Hatchet Volume 39 (Copy 1), 1942-1943 (RG0114 Series 6, Box 16)
    1 bound volume; 29 issues, 15.75" x 22.5", 4 pages (avg.)
  - Hatchet Volume 40 (Copy 1), 1943-1944 (RG0114 Series 6, Box 17)
    1 bound volume; 29 issues, 15.75" x 22.5" (issues 1-4, 29), 11.5" x 17" (issues 5-28), 4pages (all)
  - Hatchet Volume 41 (Copy 1), 1944-1945 (RG0114 Series 6, Box 17)
    1 bound volume; 27 issues, 11.25" x 16.75", 4 pages (avg.)
  - Hatchet Volume 42 (Copy 1), 1945-1946 (RG0114 Series 6, Box 18)
    2 bound volumes; 28 issues, 11.25" x 16.75", 8 pages (avg.)
  - Hatchet Volume 42 (Copy 2), 1945-1946 (RG0114 Series 6, Box 18)
  - Hatchet Volume 43 (Copy 1), 1946-1947 (Volume 43 COPY 1)
    2 bound volumes; 26 issues, plus Summer Record, 11.25" x 16.75", 8-12 pages (avg.)
  - Hatchet Volume 43 (Copy 2), 1946-1947 (RG0114 Series 6, Box 18)
  - Hatchet Volume 44 (Copy 1), 1947-1948 (RG0114 Series 6, Box 19)
    2 bound volumes; 26 issues, plus Homecoming Supplement, 16.75" x 11" (Supplement:10.5" x 15.5"), 12 pages (avg.)
  - Hatchet Volume 44 (Copy 2), 1947-1948 (RG0114 Series 6, Box 19)
  - Hatchet Volume 45 (Copy 1), 1948-1949 (Volume 45 COPY 1)
    2 bound volumes; 27 issues, plus 2 Summer Records, 11.25" x 16.5" (Summer Records:11.25" x 17"), 12 pages (avg.)
  - Hatchet Volume 45 (Copy 2), 1948-1949 (RG0114 Series 6, Box 19)
  - Hatchet Volume 46 (Copy 1), 1949-1950 (Volume 46 COPY 1)
    3 bound volumes; 26 issues, plus 2 Summer Records, 11.25" x 17" (Summer Records:11.5" x 17"), 12 pages (avg.)
  - Hatchet Volume 46 (Copy 2), 1949-1950 (RG0114 Series 6, Box 20)
  - Hatchet Volume 46 (Copy 3), 1949-1950 (RG0114 Series 6, Box 20)
  - Hatchet Volume 47 (Copy 1), 1950-1951 (Volume 47 COPY 1)
    2 bound volumes; 26 issues, plus 2 Summer Records, 11" x 16.5" (Summer Records:11.5" x 17"), 8-12 pages (avg.)
  - Hatchet Volume 47 (Copy 2), 1950-1951 (RG0114 Series 6, Box 20)
  - Hatchet Volume 48 (Copy 1), 1951-1952 (RG0114 Series 6, Box 20)
    2 bound volumes; 26 issues, plus 1 Summer Record, 11.25" x 16.75" (Summer Record:11.5" x 17"), 8 pages (avg.)
  - Hatchet Volume 48 (Copy 2), 1951-1952 (RG0114 Series 6, Box 21)
  - Hatchet Volume 49 (Copy 1), 1952-1953 (RG0114 Series 6, Box 21)
    2 bound volumes; 26 issues, 11.25" x 16.75", 8 pages (avg.)
  - Hatchet Volume 49 (Copy 2), 1952-1953 (RG0114 Series 6, Box 21)
  - Hatchet Volume 50 (Copy 1), 1953-1954 (Volume 50 COPY 1)
  - Hatchet Volume 50 (Copy 2), 1953-1954 (RG0114 Series 6, Box 22)
  - Hatchet Volume 51 (Copy 1), 1954-1955 (Volume 51 COPY 1)
    2 bound volumes; 29 issues, 11.25" x 16.75", 8 pages (avg.)
  - Hatchet Volume 51 (Copy 2), 1954-1955 (RG0114 Series 6, Box 22)
  - Hatchet Volume 52 (Copy 1), 1955-1956 (Volume 52 COPY 1)
    2 bound volumes; 27 issues, 11.25" x 16.75", 8 pages (avg.)
  - Hatchet Volume 52 (Copy 2), 1955-1956 (RG0114 Series 6, Box 22)
  - Hatchet Volume 53 (Copy 1), 1956-1957 (Volume 53 COPY 1)
    2 bound volumes; 30 issues, 11.25" x 16.75", 8-12 pages (avg.)
  - Hatchet Volume 53 (Copy 2), 1956-1957 (RG0114 Series 6, Box 22)
  - Hatchet Volume 54 (Copy 1), 1957-1958 (Volume 54 COPY 1)
    2 bound volumes; 30 issues, 11.25" x 16.75", 8 pages (avg.)
  - Hatchet Volume 54 (Copy 2), 1957-1958 (RG0114 Series 6, Box 23)
  - Hatchet Volume 55 (Copy 1), 1958-1959 (RG0114 Series 6, Box 23)
    2 bound volumes; 29 issues, 11.25" x 16.75", 8 pages (avg.), Tomahawk: 4 pages
  - Hatchet Volume 55 (Copy 2), 1958-1959 (RG0114 Series 6, Box 23)
  - Hatchet Volume 56 (Copy 1), 1959-1960 (RG0114 Series 6, Box 23)
  - Hatchet Volume 56 (Copy 2), 1959-1960 (RG0114 Series 6, Box 24)
  - Hatchet Volume 57 (Copy 1), 1960-1961 (Volume 57 COPY 1)
    2 bound volumes; In addition, there is a Jan. 1961-Dec. 1961 bound volume 29 issues, 11.25" x 16.75", 8 pages (avg.), Tomahawk: 4 pages
  - Hatchet Volume 57 (Copy 2), 1960-1961 (RG0114 Series 6, Box 24)
  - Hatchet Volumes 57-58, 1961 (Volume 57-58)
  - Hatchet Volume 58 (Copy 1), 1961-1962 (RG0114 Series 6, Box 24)
    2 bound volumes; 28 issues, plus 2 Summer Records, 11.25" x 16.75", 8 pages (avg.), Summer Records: 4 pages
  - Hatchet Volume 58 (Copy 2), 1961-1962 (RG0114 Series 6, Box 24)
  - Hatchet Volume 59 (Copy 1), 1962-1963 (Volume 59 COPY 1)
    2 bound volumes; 28 issues, plus 2 Summer Records, 11.5" x 16.75", 8 pages (avg.), Summer Records and Tomahawk: 4 pages
  - Hatchet Volume 59 (Copy 2), 1962-1963 (RG0114 Series 6, Box 25)
  - Hatchet Volume 60 (Copy 1), 1963-1964 (Volume 60 COPY 1)
    2 bound volumes; 28 issues, plus 1 Summer Record, 11.25" x 16.75" (Summer Record and Tomahawk 11.25" x 17"), 8 pages (avg.), SR and Tom.: 4 pages
  - Hatchet Volume 60 (Copy 2), 1963-1964 (RG0114 Series 6, Box 25)
  - Hatchet Volume 61 (Copy 1), 1964-1965 (RG0114 Series 6, Box 25)
    2 bound volumes; 28 issues, plus 1 Summer Record and Tomahawk, 11" x 16.75", 8 pages (avg.) Note: Tomahawk in addition to 28 regular issues
  - Hatchet Volume 61 (Copy 2), 1964-1965 (RG0114 Series 6, Box 25)
  - Hatchet Volume 62 (Copy 1), 1965-1966 (RG0114 Series 6, Box 26)
    2 bound volumes; 28 issues, plus 2 Summer Records and Election Issue, 11.25" x 16.75", 16-32 pages (avg.), Summer Records: 4-8 pages
  - Hatchet Volume 62 (Copy 2), 1965-1966 (RG0114 Series 6, Box 26)
  - Hatchet Volume 63 (Copy 1), 1966-1967 (Volume 63 COPY 1)
    2 bound volumes; 36 issues, plus 2 Summer Records, 2 Hatchet Encounters, and Tomahawk, 11" x 16.5", 12-20 pages (avg.), Summer Records (4 pages), Encounters and Tomahawk: 8 pages
  - Hatchet Volume 63 (Copy 2), 1966-1967 (RG0114 Series 6, Box 27)
  - Hatchet Volume 64 (Copy 1), 1967-1968 (Volume 64 COPY 1)
    3 bound volumes; 28 issues (no. 27 divided into 27a and 27b), plus 2 Summer Records, 5 Hatchet Encounters, and Tomahawk, 11.5" x 16.5", 20 pages (avg.),Summer Records: 4-12 pages, Encounters: 8-12 pages, Tomahawk: 4 pages
  - Hatchet Volume 64 (Copy 2), 1967-1968 (RG0114 Series 6, Box 27)
  - Hatchet Volume 64 (Copy 3), 1967-1968 (RG0114 Series 6, Box 28)
  - Hatchet Volume 65 (Copy 1), 1968-1969 (Volume 65 COPY 1)
    3 bound volumes; Hatchet begins to print bi-weekly 54 issues, plus 2 Summer Records and Tomahawk supplement, 11" x 17", 12-16 pages (avg.), Summer Records: 8 pages
  - Hatchet Volume 65 (Copy 2), 1968-1969 (RG0114 Series 6, Box 28)
  - Hatchet Volume 65 (Copy 3), 1968-1969 (RG0114 Series 6, Box 29)
  - Hatchet Volume 66 (Copy 1), 1969-1970 (Volume 66 COPY 1)
    3 bound volumes; 50 issues, plus 2 Summer Records and one supplement, 11" x 17", 12-16 pages (avg.), Summer Records: 8 pages
  - Hatchet Volume 66 (Copy 2), 1969-1970 (RG0114 Series 6, Box 29)
  - Hatchet Volume 66 (Copy 3), 1969-1970 (RG0114 Series 6, Box 30)
  - Hatchet Volume 67 (Copy 1), 1970-1971 (Volume 67 COPY 1)
    3 bound volumes; 52 issues, plus one supplement, 11" x 17", 12-20 pages (avg.)
  - Hatchet Volume 67 (Copy 2), 1970-1971 (RG0114 Series 6, Box 30)
  - Hatchet Volume 67 (Copy 3), 1970-1971 (RG0114 Series 6, Box 31)
  - Hatchet Volume 68 (Copy 1), 1971-1972 (Volume 68 COPY 1)
    3 bound volumes; 49 issues, plus Tomahawk and 2 Summer Records, 13 issues also have supplements, 10.75" x 16.75", 8-12 pages (avg.), Summer Record: 8 pages
  - Hatchet Volume 68 (Copy 2), 1971-1972 (RG0114 Series 6, Box 31)
  - Hatchet Volume 68 (Copy 3), 1971-1972 (RG0114 Series 6, Box 32)
  - Hatchet Volume 69 (Copy 1), 1972-1973 (Volume 69 COPY 1)
    3 bound volumes; 49 issues, plus 2 Summer Records, 7 supplements, 10.75" x 16.75", 8-12 pages (avg.), Summer Records: 8 pages
  - Hatchet Volume 69 (Copy 2), 1972-1973 (RG0114 Series 6, Box 32)
  - Hatchet Volume 69 (Copy 3), 1972-1973 (RG0114 Series 6, Box 33)
  - Hatchet Volume 70 (Copy 1), 1973-1974 (Volume 70 COPY 1)
  - Hatchet Volume 70 (Copy 2), 1973-1974 (RG0114 Series 6, Box 33)
  - Hatchet Volume 71 (Copy 1), 1974-1975 (Volume 71 COPY 1)
  - Hatchet Volume 71 (Copy 2), 1974-1975 (RG0114 Series 6, Box 34)
  - Hatchet Volume 72 (Copy 1), 1975-1976 (Volume 72 COPY 1)
  - Hatchet Volume 72 (Copy 2), 1975-1976 (RG0114 Series 6, Box 34)
  - Hatchet Volume 73 (Copy 1), 1976-1977 (Volume 73 COPY 1)
  - Hatchet Volume 73 (Copy 2), 1976-1977 (RG0114 Series 6, Box 35)
  - Hatchet Volume 74 (Copy 1), 1977-1978 (Volume 74 COPY 1)
    3 bound volumes; 52 issues, plus 4 Summer Records, Fall Sports supplement, Basketball preview, and Tomahawk supplement, 11.25" x 14.75", 12 pages (avg.), Summer Records: 8 pages (avg.)
  - Hatchet Volume 74 (Copy 2), 1977-1978 (RG0114 Series 6, Box 35)
  - Hatchet Volume 74 (Copy 3), 1977-1978 (RG0114 Series 6, Box 36)
  - Hatchet Volume 75 (Copy 1), 1978-1979 (Volume 75 COPY 1)
    3 bound volumes; 53 issues, plus Tomahawk supplement, 11.25" x 14.75", 16-20 pages (avg.)
  - Hatchet Volume 75 (Copy 2), 1978-1979 (RG0114 Series 6, Box 36)
  - Hatchet Volume 75 (Copy 3), 1978-1979 (RG0114 Series 6, Box 37)
  - Hatchet Volume 76 (Copy 1), 1979-1980 (Volume 76 COPY 1)
    3 bound volumes; 52 issues, (no. 38 missing), plus 2 Summer Records, 14.5" x 11.25", 16-20 pages (avg.), Summer Records: 8 pages
  - Hatchet Volume 76 (Copy 2), 1979-1980 (RG0114 Series 6, Box 37)
  - Hatchet Volume 76 (Copy 3), 1979-1980 (RG0114 Series 6, Box 38)
  - Hatchet Volume 77, Part 1 (Copy 1), 1980 (Volume 77 PART 1 COPY 1)
    2 bound volumes; Two sets of two volumes; each semester bound separately 52 issues, plus 3 Summer Records, 14.25" x 11.25", 20 pages (avg.), Summer Records: 12 pages (avg.)
  - Hatchet Volume 77, Part 2 (Copy 1), 1981 (Volume 77 PART 2 COPY 1)
  - Hatchet Volume 77, Part 1 (Copy 2), 1980 (RG0114 Series 6, Box 38)
  - Hatchet Volume 77, Part 2 (Copy 2), 1981 (RG0114 Series 6, Box 39)
  - Hatchet Volume 78 (Copy 1), 1981-1982 (Volume 78 COPY 1)
    2 bound volumes; 51 issues, plus Winter Sports preview, 14.25" x 11.25", 16-24 pages (avg.)
  - Hatchet Volume 78 (Copy 2), 1981-1982 (RG0114 Series 6, Box 39)
  - Hatchet Volume 79 (Copy 1), 1982-1983 (Volume 79 COPY 1)
    1 bound volume; 2 loose boxed volumes; 50 issues, plus Winter Sports preview, 14.25" x 11.25", 16-20 pages (avg.)
  - Hatchet Volume 79 (Copy 2), 1982-1983 (RG0114 Series 6, Box 40)
  - Hatchet Volume 79 (Copy 3), 1982-1983 (RG0114 Series 6, Box 40)
  - Hatchet Volume 80 (Copy 1), 1983-1984 (Volume 80 COPY 1)
    2 volumes; 51 loose boxed issues each, 14.25" x 11.25", 16-20 pages (avg.)
  - Hatchet Volume 80 (Copy 2), 1983-1984 (RG0114 Series 6, Box 41)
  - Hatchet Volume 81 (Copy 1), 1984-1985 (RG0114 Series 6, Box 42)
    2 volumes; 48 loose boxed issues each, plus one supplement, 14.25" x 11.25", 20 pages (avg.)
  - Hatchet Volume 82 (Copy 1), 1985-1986 (RG0114 Series 6, Box 43)
    2 volumes; 49 loose boxed issues each, 14.25" x 11.25", 20 pages (avg.)
  - Hatchet Volume 83 (Copy 1), 1986-1987 (RG0114 Series 6, Box 44)
    2 volumes; 52 loose boxed issues, plus one supplement, 14.5" x 11.25", 20 pages (avg.)
  - Hatchet Volume 83 (Copy 2), 1986-1987 (RG0114 Series 6, Box 44)
  - Hatchet Volume 84 (Copy 1), 1987-1988 (RG0114 Series 6, Box 45)
    2 volumes; 50 loose boxed issues each, 14.5" x 11.5", 20-24 pages (avg.)
  - Hatchet Volume 84 (Copy 2), 1987-1988 (RG0114 Series 6, Box 45)
  - Hatchet Volume 85 (Copy 1), 1988-1989
    2 volumes; loose boxed issues
  - Hatchet Volume 85 (Copy 2), 1988-1989 (RG0114 Series 6, Box 46)
  - Hatchet Volume 86 (Copy 1), 1989-1990 (RG0114 Series 6, Box 47)
  - Hatchet Volume 86 (Copy 2), 1989-1990; Series 6 (Volume 86 COPY 2)
    1 bound volume; Loose copies (no bound volume); missing nos. 42, 44
  - Hatchet Volume 87 (Copy 1), 1990-1991; Series 6 (Volume 87 COPY 1)
    2 volumes; First copy in bound volume (complete); second copy are individual issues boxed (missing nos. 1, 2, 55, 56)
  - Hatchet Volume 87 (Copy 2), 1990-1991 (RG0114 Series 6, Box 48)
  - Hatchet Volume 87 (Copy 3), 1990-1991
  - Hatchet Volume 88 (Copy 1), 1991-1992; Series 6 (Volume 88 COPY 1)
    2 volumes; (missing nos. 1 and 47)
  - Hatchet Volume 88 (Copy 2), 1991-1992 (RG0114 Series 6, Box 49)
  - Hatchet Volume 89 (Copy 1), 1992-1993; Series 6 (Volume 89 COPY 1)
  - Hatchet Volume 89 (Copy 2), 1992-1993
  - Hatchet Volume 90 (Copy 1), 1993-1994; Series 6 (Volume 90 COPY 1)
  - Hatchet Volume 90 (Copy 2), 1993-1994 (RG0114 Series 6, Box 50)
  - Hatchet Volume 91 (Copy 1), 1994-1995; Series 6 (Volume 91 COPY 1)
  - Hatchet Volume 91 (Copy 2), 1994-1995 (RG0114 Series 6, Box 51)
  - Hatchet Volume 92 (Copy 1), 1995-1996; Series 6 (Volume 92 COPY 1)
  - Hatchet Volume 92 (Copy 2), 1995-1996 (RG0114 Series 6, Box 52)
  - Hatchet Volume 93 (Copy 1), 1996-1997; Series 6 (Volume 93 COPY 1)
  - Hatchet Volume 93 (Copy 2), 1996-1997 (RG0114 Series 6, Box 53)
  - Hatchet Volume 94, Part 1 (Copy 1), 1997 (Volume 94 PART 1 COPY 1)
    2 volumes; First copy in bound volume (complete); second copy are individual issues boxed (complete)
  - Hatchet Volume 94, Part 2 (Copy 1), 1998 (Volume 94 PART 2 COPY 1)
  - Hatchet Volume 94 (Copy 2), 1997-1998 (RG0114 Series 6, Box 54)
  - Hatchet Volume 95 (Copy 1), 1998-1999; Series 6 (Volume 95 COPY 1)
  - Hatchet Volume 95 (Copy 2), 1998-1999 (RG0114 Series 6, Box 55)
  - Hatchet Volume 96 (Copy 1), 1999-2000; Series 6 (Volume 96 COPY 1)
  - Hatchet Volume 96 (Copy 2), 1999-2000 (RG0114 Series 6, Box 56)
  - Hatchet Volume 97 (Copy 1), 2000-2001; Series 6 (Volume 97 COPY 1)
  - Hatchet Volume 97 (Copy 2), 2000-2001 (RG0114 Series 6, Box 57)
  - Hatchet Volume 98 (Copy 1), 2001-2002; Series 6 (Volume 98 COPY 1)
  - Hatchet Volume 98 (Copy 2), 2001-2002 (RG0114 Series 6, Box 58)
  - Hatchet Volume 99 (Copy 1), 2002-2003 (Volume 99 COPY 1)
  - Hatchet Volume 99 (Copy 2), 2002-2003 (RG0114 Series 6, Box 59)
  - Hatchet Volume 100 (Copy 1), 2003-2004; Series 6 (Volume 100 COPY 1)
  - Hatchet Volume 100 (Copy 2), 2003-2004 (RG0114 Series 6, Box 60)
  - Hatchet Volume 101 (Copy 1), 2004-2005; Series 6 (Volume 101 COPY 1)
  - Hatchet Volume 101 (Copy 2), 2004-2005 (RG0114 Series 6, Box 61)
  - Hatchet Volume 102 (Copy 1), 2005-2006; Series 6 (Volume 102 COPY 1)
  - Hatchet Volume 102 (Copy 2), 2005-2006 (RG0114 Series 6, Box 62)
  - Hatchet Volume 103 (Copy 1), 2006-2007; Series 6 (Volume 103 COPY 1)
    2 boxes of individual issues. Copy one complete, copy two missing issues.
  - Hatchet Volume 103 (Copy 2), 2006-2007 (RG0114 Series 6, Box 62)